Yuna-chan, it's been a while.
ゆなちゃん、久しぶり
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
How have you been?
元気だった?
How many months has it been since?
何か月ぶり?
It's been about 3 or 4 months.
3、4か月ぶりくらいか
It's still cute.
相変わらず可愛いですね
Today too.
今日も
Have you played with guys since then?
あれから男の人と遊んだ?
I'm not playing.
遊んでないです
Have you never played?
一回も遊んでないの?
Does that mean you haven't even had sex?
ってことはエッチもしてないってこと?
yes.
はい
That's right.
そうなんだ
Will the number of experienced people remain at 2?
経験人数2人のまま?
yes.
はい
It's a waste.
もったいないね
It's so cute.
こんな可愛いんだよね
Have you kept your promise?
例の約束守ってきた?
What kind of promise?
どんな約束だっけ?
No plan no par.
ノープラノーパー
Did you come all this way with no plan or par?
ノープラノーパーでここまで来るって?
Are you really protecting it?
ほんと守ってんの?
yes.
はい
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってみて
I've been protecting it properly.
ちゃんと守ってきたんだ
Didn't you get teased?
チカンされなかった?
On the way?
途中で?
That was not the case.
そうなかったです
Wouldn't it have been terrible if it had been found out?
バレたらやばかった?
It was a thump.
ドギドギだったね
Turn around.
後ろを向いて
Do that a lot.
それまくって
Butt.
お尻
More properly.
もっとちゃんと
Stick your butt out here.
お尻こっち突き出して
Open your legs more.
もっと足開いて
It's a waste.
もったいないね
Such a nice butt.
こんないいお尻なのに
I can't help but go with only two people.
2人としかいっちゃしょうがないし
One of them is really perverted.
うち1人はすげえ変態だし
No bra really.
ほんとにノーブラノー
Try to guess like this.
こうやって当ててみて
Is it see-through?
透 けるかどうか
It's a little transparent.
ちょっと透けてるね
Take a look.
ちょっと見てみて
Sit down for a moment.
ちょっとお座って
I had a pussy for the first time in 3 months.
3ヶ月ぶりにマンコミして
Are you nervous?
緊張してんの?
緊張してる?
Open it.
開いて
Open your legs more.
もっと開いて足
Open it yourself.
自分で開いて
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Please open it up more.
もっと開いてあげて
Stick it out.
突き出して
You can see deep into your nose.
鼻の奥まで見えるよ
That's a really erotic pussy.
すんごいエロいマンコだね
Erotic idol pussy.
エロいアイドルのマンコ
Isn't it beautiful?
綺麗じゃない?
It's pink.
ピンク色だよ
I don't think it's from here.
こ っからはないと思う
Try it yourself.
自分で触り触ってみて
The open one is black.
開いた方が黒じゃん
Do you always do that?
いつもそうやってるの?
Alone.
一人で
You're doing it, right?
やってるでしょ?
Actually.
本当は
Hide.
隠れて
You're used to your fingers.
指慣れてんじゃん
I do it all the time.
いつもやってるもんね
Instead of playing with men, she does it herself.
男と遊ばない代わりに自分でやってるもんね
Look back.
振り見して
Look at your face.
顔見て
Great, you're standing still.
すんげえ立ってんじゃん
Does that feel good?
そこが気持ちいいの?
Are you always messing around there?
いつもそこばっかいじってんの?
It's getting wet here.
ここ濡れてきてるよ
Kuribinbin.
くりびんびん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Now it's time for the fourth one.
今度4つ目だい
So you want me to pull up my pants myself?
それで自分でパンツ上げてもらう?
It's black.
黒じゃん
Is it open yet?
まだ開いたの?
This way.
こっちを
Butthole.
お尻の穴
Raise only one leg.
片足の足だけ上げて
The black jacket is open
黒じゃん開いた
of?
の?
Did you touch it?
く り触ったの?
It's standing up.
くり立ってるよ
It's amazing.
すんげえびんびんじゃん
Take a close look.
もっかい目視して
Make sure to pull up your pants.
ちゃんとパンツ上げて
Do your own nipples.
自分で乳首して
Try raising your nipples yourself.
自分で乳首立ってみて
You're already standing.
もう立ってんじゃん
Visually.
目視して
Pussy with one hand.
片手でまんこして
Peace.
ピースして
Properly.
ちゃん と
Now, try standing this neck up.
じゃあこのネック立ってみて
It's cute.
かわいいね
Try some poses.
なんかポーズしてみて
Be a cute girl.
かわいい子にして
Is there an idol pose?
アイドルポーズあるだろ?
Then give me cute breasts.
じゃあかわいいおっぱいにして
Try talking.
喋ってみて
It's so sexy.
すんげえちくり立ってるよ
You look so sassy.
こんなセースな顔してんのにね
Kuri-chan must have eaten a lot.
くりちゃんいっぱいすったんじゃん
There is no opposition.
反対もない
Kuri-chan, the ribbon is in the way, so I'll take it away.
くりちゃん、リボン邪魔だから取っちゃうよ
Also, the skirt is coming out.
あとスカートも出ちゃってるよ
Raise your feet.
足上げて
My pussy is tingling.
おまんこヒクヒクしてるよ
Kuri-chan, come here.
くりちゃんこっちおいで
Look this way.
こっち向いてほら
Put it inside Kuri-chan's hole.
くりちゃん穴の中も入れて
Put the whole bottom in.
下全部入れて
Stir it inside.
中でかき回して
Kuri-chan, smoke a lot of chestnuts.
くりちゃん栗いっぱい吸ってこんで
You like chestnuts, right?
栗好きだろ?
栗好きでしょ?
Take a look at the hole once.
一 回穴見してほら
Spread it out.
広げて
Look, Kuri-chan.
見してほら、くりちゃん
Expand the hole.
穴広げて
Yes, curl up
そう、くりくりして
Ru.
る
Kuri-chan, it's all inside her butt.
く りちゃん、お尻の中が全部
Up to the top.
上 まで
Show your butt more.
もっとお尻つき出して
Lick all the inside of your ass.
お尻の中いっぱい舐めて
Have you ever been licked?
舐められたことある?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Does it feel weird?
変な感じ?
Kuri-chan, everything up to her pussy.
くりちゃん、まんこまで全部
From the butt.
お尻から
Kuriman.
くりまん
From the butt.
お尻からで
Insert it properly into the hole.
穴にもちゃんと入れて
Yuuna-chan, try making it yourself.
ゆうなちゃん、自分でくりいじってみ
Kuru-chan, throw it in the hole.
くるちゃん、穴の中投げて
Open it.
開いて
Kuru-chan, inside her asshole.
くるちゃん、ケツ穴の中
Kuru-chan, bring me the phone.
くるちゃん、電話持ってきて
This is a naughty position.
エッチな体勢、これ
Try opening it yourself.
自分でそっち開いてみて
It's wet.
ぬれぬれじゃん
Pussy.
おまんこ
hey.
ね
Clear it.
クリアしてやって
Hold it yourself like this.
自分でこうやって持って
Look at all the pussies.
おまんこいっぱい見てな
Kuru-chan, can I turn it to where there is a hole?
くるちゃん、穴あるところに回していい?
Shall I put it in?
入れちゃう?
I think I'm going to go in.
入っちゃいそう
I'm going in.
入っちゃう
I went in.
入 っちゃった
入っちゃった
Awesome, amazing.
すごいすごい
It's all in.
全部入っちゃった
Try turning it slowly.
ゆっくり回してみな
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's mellow.
めろいな
Kuru-chan, show me from the side.
くるちゃん、横から見せて
Let go once.
一回離してみ
Let go.
離してみ
It stung.
刺さったよ
You understand, right?
分かるでしょ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Did you know it felt good?
気持ちいいと分かってた?
I saw that face.
その顔見てたよ
It's so erotic.
すごいエロい
Kuru-chan, let's take turns.
くるちゃん、交代してみ
hand.
て
Try pulling it out slowly.
ゆ っくり抜いてみな
Just spread it out.
そのまま広げて
Erotic.
エロ
Amazing amazing.
すごい すごい
Too erotic.
エロいすぎる
Try bringing it yourself.
自分で持っていってみて
Come.
くる
Kuru-chan, can I enter this hole?
くるちゃん、この穴入っちゃいい?
Chan, please look again.
ちゃん、見直して
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
This angel is dripping.
このアンジュル垂れてきた
Amazing Japanese light.
すごい日本ライト
Kuru-chan, here.
くるちゃん、ここ
It came out a mess.
くちゃくちゃ出てきた
out
出
It's here.
て きたよ
stomach
い
It's blowing salt.
っぱ い塩吹いてる
Butt.
お尻
Did you spray salt?
塩吹いちゃったの?
Hey.
ねえ
Try taking turns.
交代してみて
Amazing Japanese light.
すごい日本ライト
It's so erotic.
すごいエロいじゃん
Good, good, good.
よいしょよいしょ
Look.
見して
A lot of things came out.
なんかいっぱい出てきたよ
I'm watching Kuru go.
くるが行くとこ見してる
Did you see it?
見てたの?
Shall I nibble it with my fingers?
指でかじまわしておく?
Mom.
お 母ちゃん
Could you please see where everyone is going?
みんな行くとこ見てもらえ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Yeah.
うん
Look.
見して
Erotic pussy.
エロいまんこ
I sprayed a lot of salt on it.
いっぱい塩吹いちゃったじゃん
Hey.
ねえ
Was it your first time blowing it?
初めて吹いたの?
Can I post something more erotic?
もっとエロいのぶち込んじゃっていい?
It's pink.
ピンクいやつだ
A nice light to hold.
足持っていいライト
Look at me making pressure points.
ツボツボしてるとこ見して
If you stab it slowly.
ゆっくり刺したら
I'll take it slow.
ゆっくりお踏まえる
Acupuncture points.
ツボツボ
Look here.
こっち見て
There are buns dripping on the floor.
床にまんじんがたれてる
Please turn on the vibration.
振動かけにしてね
That's how you get it moving.
そう やって動かしてもらう
There's going to be a lot.
いっぱい出ちゃうじゃん
Put this thick one in.
こんな太いの入れて
I blew salt.
塩吹いちゃって
amazing.
すごい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Erotic.
エロい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Look this way.
こっち向いてほら
You must have been blowing a lot.
いっぱい吹いちゃってんじゃん
Please turn around a lot.
いっぱい向き直してあげな
Does this feel good?
これ気持ちいいの?
I'll have more of you.
もっといっぱいついてもらう
This is amazing.
すごいねこれ
It won't stop.
止まんないじゃん
It's been flying forever.
ずっと飛んでんじゃん
Show me that hole.
それ穴見せて
Spread it out and show me.
広げて見せて
a,
あ、
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
うん、 うん、うん
I'll try putting more.
もっと置いてみる
Do you want to come out because it feels good?
気持ちよくて出ちゃうの?
ah.
ああ
Don't hide your hands.
手をかくさない
Look here.
こっち見な
It won't stop.
止まんないじゃん
I've been able to cross.
渡れてきたよ
This is an erotic pussy.
エロいマン子だねこれ
Yuma-chan.
ゆうまちゃん
I did this though.
こんなしちゃったけど
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It was so salty.
めちゃめちゃ塩吹いた
Your eyes felt good, right?
目、気持ちよかったでしょ?
first time?
初めて?
Did you blow it?
あんの、吹いたの?
yes.
はい
Listen, this is your first time blowing it?
いいか、吹いたのが初めて?
It was very good.
しょうがいろかったよ
Give this to me.
これさ、あげてみて
What is this?
なんですか、これは?
Chin chin.
ちんちん
Chin Chin?
ちんちん?
Can you feel it?
手触ってごらん?
Bring your face closer.
もっと顔近づけて
Look at me
こっち見なが
and others.
ら
Is it getting bigger?
大 きくなってきた?
It's like Saki-ish.
さきっぽいしって
Let me give you a chew.
チューしてもらおう
Properly.
ちゃんと
all.
全部
Great imitation.
大まね
Put it on your face.
顔に当てて
Complete.
全
Opposition.
反対
Go to sleep.
寝ろよ
How does it make you feel?
どんな気分になる?
Feeling naughty?
えっちゃな気分になる?
Well then, take out your tongue.
じゃあ、ベロ出して
Just throw it at me
さきっぽちろちろ投げてごら
yeah.
ん
Give me more of your tongue.
も っとベロいっぱい出して
all.
全部
I'm drenched in saliva.
唾だらして
Get all wet with your chest.
胸ぬれにして全部
Throw it by chance.
たまたま投げて
Throw more.
もっといっぱい投げて
Try putting all the bullets in your mouth.
口に弾全部入れてみて
While looking at me.
こっち見ながら
So reach out.
それで手を伸ばして
Just make more noise.
もっといっぱい音だけ出して
I need to include more of everything.
もっと全部入れなくちゃ
You can park.
パークってできるやん
It's in there.
入ってるじゃん
by chance.
たまたま
Bellow all the way to the top.
上までベローっと
Let's talk dick as hard as we can.
思いっきりチンコ喋っとく
Hands get in the way.
手邪魔
While facing this way.
こっち向きながら
Make me salivate more.
もっといっぱい唾だらして
Faster.
もっと早く
Suck a lot.
いっぱい吸う
That's amazing, Chin Chin.
すごいよ、チンチン
Okay?
おっけー?
My left hand just happened to be there.
左手はたまたまだって
Shall I feed you?
もんであげる?
Deeper.
もっと奥まで
To the deepest part.
一番奥まで
Next time I'll use my hands too.
今度は手も使ってやったら
If you talk a lot about people.
人をいっぱい喋ったら
Have a look at Chin Chin?
チンチン見してみ?
Shall I feed you?
もんであげるか
Come next to my face.
顔隣に来て
Let's compare.
比べておこう
Erotic?
エロい?
chatter
喋
That's it.
って
Use your hands too.
手 も使って
Please jerk off.
シコシコしてね
Make more noise.
もっと音立って
Would you like to jerk off?
シコシコしてごらん?
Tip.
先っぽ
Drool.
唾垂らして
While licking the tip.
先っぽ舐めながら
Place it from below.
下から置いとく
You can't take it from here.
こっちから取っちゃダメだよ
Got it?
分かった?
Don't pull it out.
抜いちゃダメだよ
More high pink.
もっとハイピンク
Suck more, chin chin.
もっと吸って、チンチン
With tongue.
ベロで
While salivating a lot.
いっぱい唾垂らしながら
A place that moves.
動いていく場所
I don't mind being pushed in the head.
頭押されてもいいから
To the back.
奥まで
Hands get in the way.
手邪魔
more.
もっと
Not yet.
まだダメ
more.
もっと
Look this way.
こっち向いて
While facing.
向きながら
Faster.
もっと早く
Lots of shadow.
いっぱいシャドウ
While looking at me.
こっち見ながら
Going forward.
ゆくゆく
To the back.
奥まで
My head was pushed.
頭押されて
cold.
寒い
I was so frustrated that I cried.
悔しくて泣いちゃったもん
Shall we go to bed?
ベッドに行こうか
Fukuro-chan, sleep there.
ふくろちゃん、そこ寝て
Mena-chan, come on.
めなちゃん、おいで
Fiddle with your hands again.
もう一回手でいじって
While making more faces.
もっと顔しながら
Spit on it.
ツバ垂らして
Put on all the saliva.
ツバ全部つけて
I happened to touch it and shed tears.
たまたま触りながら、涙とか
Saki-ish jittery.
さきっぽいじったり
I tried turning this.
こ っち回してみた
Lick the back muscles all over.
裏筋いっぱい舐めて
Go all the way and step.
一番奥まで行って、ステップして
Fukuro-chan, keep your head over there.
ふくろちゃん、頭あっちにして
Mina-chan, please wash your hands.
みなちゃん、しっくさんして
A lot of shadow.
いっぱいシャドウに
My pussy is being licked.
おまんこ舐められてる
Fukuro-chan, please open up more.
ふくろちゃん、もっと開いて
Please suck my clitoris fully.
クリトリスいっぱい吸ってあげな
Please put your finger in.
指入れてください
Try squeezing it.
しこしこしてみて
Looks like Saki-ish.
さきっぽいっぽい
That's nice, Chan-chan.
かったいな、ちゃんちゃん
Speak.
喋って
I'll go myself next time.
自分で今度は行く
Fukuro-chan, do your best.
ふ くろちゃん、思いっきり思いっきり
Fukuro-chan, do you want to remember?
ふくろちゃん、思い入れたい?
Finally, try your hardest faster.
最後、もっと早く思いっきり
Faster.
も っと早く
Fukuro-chan, let's go now.
ふくろちゃん、 そろそろ行っちゃおう
Yuuka-chan, go to sleep.
ゆうかちゃん、お寝てよ
I should also go to the home.
俺もホームに行ってみて
Get some sleep.
ゆっくり寝てごらん
That's nice, Chan-chan.
かったいね、ちゃんちゃん
slowly.
ゆっくり
Chinchindo?
ちんちんどう?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It goes very deep.
すごく奥まで入ってる
Do you know it's all the way inside?
奥まで入ってるの分かる?
I was sleeping in Manjul due to the shaking.
マンジュルで揺れに寝てたよ
Try touching the chestnut.
くり触ってみて
Try it yourself.
自分でくり触ってみて
The juice is dripping.
汁垂れてきた
Fukuro-chan, turn around.
ふ く ろ ちゃん、後ろ回って
Fukuro-chan, go deeper.
ふくろちゃん、もっと奥まで
It's about time.
そろそろ
It's the deepest part.
一番奥ついたんよ
Take a look once.
一回向いてごらん
Just keep your feet.
足そのまま
Fukuro-chan says the hole is wide.
穴が広いって、ふくろちゃん
Manko was crying.
マン子は泣いちゃったね
Surprisingly.
ばっくり
Just stand still and come here.
そのまま立ってこっち来な
Butt facing this way.
お尻こっち向いてこっち
Open your legs more.
もっと足開けよ
Show me your face with dick in it.
ちんちゃん入ってる顔見せて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
Yeah, it feels good.
うん、気持ちいいです
Fukuro-chan, raise your leg.
ふくろちゃん、足あげて
I can see everything.
全部見えるよ
My body is shaking.
体ガクガクして
I can't open it, so come to bed.
開けないからベッドおいでほら
This way.
こっち向き
Show your butt to Fukuro-chan.
ふくろちゃんにお尻つき出して
Make it more and more intense.
どんどん激しくして
Did you go again?
また行っちゃった?
Because it's not over yet.
まだ終わんないから
Finally put it in my pillow.
ついに枕に入れて
Spit it out too.
お前も吐き回して
To the deepest part.
一番奥まで
So cute.
かわいくらい
Please comb it again.
もう一回くしざしやってください
Use your legs as much as you can.
足を思いっきり
Do you say chin chin yourself?
自分でチンチン言うとか
You can see a lot of places inside.
入ってるところいっぱい見えるよ
So go all out.
それで思いっきり
Move your hips.
腰動かしてね
Finally, follow Fukuro-chan.
ふくろちゃんに従わるついに
Yes, then.
はい、そしたら
So do it.
それでやって
I'll only do the last part.
本当最後のところだけやるから
hey.
ね
Get behind me.
後 ろについて
M.G.D.
MGDが
Move your hips.
腰動かして
Fukuro-chan is also in good health.
ふくろちゃんも体調を
Did you go again?
また行っちゃったの?
Just lie there.
そこに寝てごらん
Sleep with a comfortable pussy.
いっぱいおまん気持ちよくして寝て
Look, Fukuro-chan.
ふ く ろちゃんほら
My curls are dripping.
まんじる垂れてるよ
Pour in all of Fukuro-chan.
ふくろちゃん全部流し入れ
I gave you a lot, Fukuro-chan.
いっぱい出したよ、ふくろちゃん
Here, scrape it out with your fingers.
ほら、指でかき出して
Clean this up.
これきれいにして
How was Yuna-chan?
ゆなちゃんどうだった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Let's do it again next time.
また次もやろうよ
good?
いい?